Marshland
The Parade Ground
Königsplatz
The Empire
The Victory Column
The Old Palace
Foundations
The First Courses
Walls Rising
The Shell
Finished
The Square Laid Out
The Empire at Its Height
First Motor Cars
The Horse Tram
Electric Trams
Mobilisation
The Inscription
The Republic
Black, Red, Gold
Hard Times
The Twenties
Depression
The Fire
Burnt Out
Empty
The Column Is Gone
Blackout
Bomb Damage
The Battle
The Flag on the Roof
The Ruin in Daylight
Vegetable Gardens
The Great Rally
Clearing
The Dome Comes Down
The Bare Ruin
The Wall
Reconstruction
Halfway
Reopened
The Death Strip
Graffiti
Anniversary
The Wall Falls
Reunification
The Wall Comes Down
The Scar
Wrapped
Unwrapped
Rebuilding
The Glass Dome
The Queue
The Government Quarter
The Fan Zone
Solar and Cycles
Full Season
Empty
Life Returns
Present Day